Simon, Fanny Records 5169
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Spanish Booklets Folder 3, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Quinto Congreso Obrero Cooperativista, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By Gran Partido Socialista del Sureste. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Resena de la Historia de un Rio, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By Lazaro B. Grattarola. Item is in Spanish.
- Spanish Booklets Folder 4, 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Confederacion Sindical Unitaria de Mexico, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    By Seccion de la Confederacion Sindical Latinoamericana y de la Internacional Sindical Roja. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Espacio Tiempo Historico, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    By Victor R. Haya de la Torre. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Ex-Combatientes y Desocupados, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    By V. R. Haya de la Torre. Item is in Spanish.
- Spanish Booklets Folder 5, 1936-1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Guatemala en Cifras, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By Direccion General de Estadistica. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Danzas Folkloricas Argentinas, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By Lazaro Flury. sintesis de su origen y coreografia (con un apendice de danzas indigenas ineditas). Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Senderos de Libertad, Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By Ministerio de Educacion Publica. Item is in Spanish.
- L, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Voto salvado del Diputado por el Distrito Federal, Doctor Luis Lander, al ultimo Mensaje del ex-Presidente de la Republica, General E. Lopez Contreras, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Doctor Luis Lander. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Post-War Problems of Brazil, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Latin American Economic Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: La economia asunto de todos, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Abba P. Lerner. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Catalogo General, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Libreria y Editorial "La Vanguardia". Nuestras Publicaciones el Pequeno Libro Socialista Ediciones Sociedad Luz y Biblioteca Racionalista. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: La Doctrina Socialista y su interpretacion en el articulo 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Vincente Lombardo Toledano. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Entre dos Fuegos, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    By Analuisa Llovera. Item is in Spanish.
- M, 1937; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Los Derechos Sindicales de los Trabajadores Intelectuales, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Fifth Column in Mexico, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    By Vicente Lombardo Toledano. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Dos Ideologias y Dos Culturas, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    By Dra. Paulina Luisi. Item is in Spanish.
- M, 1937-1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Agricultural Economy of El Salvador, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    By Fritz Loenholdt. Item is in Spanish.
- N, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: La Iglesia Catolica y La Reforma de la Constitucion Argentina, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Celedonio Nin y Silva. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Los Alzados y Sindicato, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Luis Octavio Madero. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Folletos Escogidos, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Casimiro Olaneta. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Costa Rica: Documentos para la Historia, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Organizacion Regional Interamericana del Trabajo. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Sentido Social de la Libertad, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    By Arturo Orgaz. 2 copies. Item is in Spanish.
- O, 1939; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: El Problema del Proletariado en Mexico, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    By Roberto Quiros Martinez. Item is in Spanish.
- P, 1897-1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Certamen Internacional de La Protesta, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By Certamen Internacional. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: El Congreso de Panama (1826), Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By Raul Porras Barrenechea. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de Trabajo Celebrando entre Cerveceria C.A.S.A. y el Sindicato, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By Pacto Colectivo de Condiciones de Trabajo. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Quienes traicionaron al pueblo, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By Magda Portal. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Figuras y Figurones, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    By Manuel G. Prada. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Nuevas Paginas Libres, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Q, 1930; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Tirania y Demagogia, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    By Alfredo L. Palacios. La Libre Navegacion de los Rios. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Juventud Aprista Peruana, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    By Partido Aprista Peruano Federacion Aprista Juvenil. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Plataforma Politica para la Administracion Orlich, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    By Comite de Planes del Partido Liberacion Nacional. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: La Cuestion Agraria Mexicana, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
- R, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Historia Economica do Brasil 1500-1820, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
    By Roberto C. Simonsen. Item is in Portuguese.
  - Item 2: Historia Economica do Brasil 1500-1820 Tomo II, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- R, 1955; Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Revista de Derecho Industrial, Publication (Box 6, Folder 2)
    By Lic. Aquiles Cruz. 6 copies. Item is in Portuguese.
- S, 1956-1957; Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Curso Breve de Psicologia Educativa, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Rafael Ramirez. Item is in Portuguese.
  - Item 2: Como Nace y Se Desarrolla una Cooperativa, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Nicolas Repetto. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: Revista del Archivo de la Biblioteca Nacional, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Biblioteca Nacional de Quito. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Mitre e Osorio na Guerra do Paraguai, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By Rodolfo Rivarola. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Libro Primero de la Escuela Elemental Peruana, Publication (Box 6, Folder 3)
    By E. Ponce Rodriguez. Item is in Spanish.
- T, 1933-1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: La Perspectiva de la Medicina en lo Seguros Sociales, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Garcia Tello. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Estructurando la Medicina del Futuro, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Etnologia y Etnografia de Guatemala, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    By Franz Termer. Item is in Spanish.
- U, 1931; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: El Nivel de Vida, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Mariano R. Tissembaum. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: La VIII Conferencia Panamericana "Otra Comedia?", Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Haya de la Torre. 2 copies. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 3: The Mexican Government's Six Year Plan, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Trens Agency - News for Newspapers. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: La Primera Pieza Teatral Argentina, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Universidad Nacional del Litoral. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: La Conferencia de Montevideo, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Union Republica Latina. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 6: Finalidades de la Universidad, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    By Universidad Obrera de Mexico. Item is in Spanish.
- V, 1950-1960; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Caribbean Islands and the War, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By United States Department of State. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Revista de Filosofia, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Facultad de Ciencias y Letras. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Congresos Americanos de Lima, Tomo II, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Alberto Ulloa. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: Informea la Asamblea General1931, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Union Linotipografica. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Asamblea General Ordinaria, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    By Union Obrera Textil. Item is in Spanish.
- W, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agenda del Maestro, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By J. Rubio Villagran y Carlos Peza de la Vega. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 2: Regards Sur Le Monde Indo-Latin, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By Auguste P. Vistel. Item is in French.
  - Item 3: Discurso con Occasion de la XIII Graduacion de la Escuela Agricola Panamericana de el Zamorano, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By Doctor Ramon Villeda Morales. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 4: El Problema Social de la Medicina en Honduras, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By Dr. Ramon Villeda Morales. Item is in Spanish.
  - Item 5: Discurso del Ciudadano Presidente de la Republica, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Avance del Imperialismo Facista en el Peru, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    By Leon de Vivero. Item is in Spanish.
- Z, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: O Acucar sob o Governo Getulio Vargas, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By D.N.P. Item is in Portuguese.
  - Item 2: Atualidade Brasileira: Seus Problemas e Solucoes, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By Getulio Vargas. Item is in Portuguese.
  - Item 3: Manuel Gonzalez Prada, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    By Luis Velazco Aragon. Item is in Spanish.
- Z, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: O Acucar sob o Governo Getulio Vargas, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Atualidade Brasileira: Seus Problemas e Solucoes, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Manuel Gonzalez Prada, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Z, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: O Acucar sob o Governo Getulio Vargas, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Atualidade Brasileira: Seus Problemas e Solucoes, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Manuel Gonzalez Prada, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)